[music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Command Center Postgame Live is brought
to you by Nissan. You deserve a car that
thrills you. And Nissan's got an
exciting full line that'll [music] put
goosebumps on your goosebumps.
Experience the thrill for yourself. Shop
your local Nissan store and [music]
Nissanusa.com
today.
Welcome into Command Center Postgame
Live brought to you by [music] Nissan.
Your final score, you seeing that right,
24- 17 out here in Philly. And I'm here
with some great guys. Ron Kova Jr. here
with Brian Mitchell and Santana Moss.
And boy, does it feel good to get a W
for the last one of the season, fellas.
Well, if you're sitting in that tunnel
and you watch all the guys coming off
the field from players to coaches and
people around this team, you understand
it's very hard to win in this league.
And I understand a lot of people are
upset how the year is gone. But when you
have injuries and all those type of
things, you still keep fighting. You
still feel you can win because
everybody's a pro in this league. And to
see them come through there, you can see
the relief on their faces. This is the
last game. At least it gives you a great
taste of what you can go into the
offseason with. And I saw a lot of guys
that were fighting out there. I saw a
lot of coaches like, "Woo Lord, we got
it done." I know. Listen,
>> don't say tell about who the Eagles
played. Hell playing back.
[music]
>> [music]
>> going to talk about all that. But
fellas, let's bask in this moment right
now because we talked about what this
game meant for us, but we knew what it
meant for the Eagles. They were playing
for second place, right? They did not
get that because of us today. And
you said it perfectly. Yes, they played
their backups.
>> Yeah,
>> they had their backup quarterback in. We
had our third string quarterback in. And
we have had to play with that all
season,
>> but they had a lot of starters in, too.
>> They had a lot of starters in and we
have had to play like that all season
long. So, to all those fans that are are
poo pooing on us saying that Philly had
their backups, well, we play with
backups all season long. And it shows
how hard that is to do. Be it.
>> It's hard to get it done. But you know
what? When you look at this game for me,
I saw some great things on defense. I
saw Jeremy Reeds out there running
around, got a pick, did some great first
pick since 2020. Okay. I saw some great
things happening. I also saw, we've been
talking about we have a young good
running back. We got two young good
running backs. Okay. Crod has shown you
he can outright ball as well. All right.
Bill can play. Crock can ball, too. I
saw guys stepping up and that offensive
line was good as well. And somebody that
definitely stepped up was our
quarterback Josh Johnson. He is headed
to the podium right now. Let's check out
our boy.
>> Nobody in here.
>> Hold on. Hey, come on one second.
>> Yeah. I mean, we out.
You with me? You ready to go? Look at
it.
>> You ready to get to that Sunday dinner,
huh? Hey, look. We got to get one.
>> I feel you.
[sighs]
They're probably all waiting to come in
line.
>> Well, I mean,
>> we got we got
>> You want to You want to get the party
going?
>> What's it like to get the win, man?
>> What's it like to get the win?
>> Uh,
it's unexplainable, man. Like, I know to
the rest of the world this might not
mean nothing, but uh just the journey
I've been on. Um, last time I was in
this building, I thought my career was
over and uh to just go out here and just
just win today. Not just win, but how we
win, man. It was like adversity,
interception. We we fumbled a snap. You
know, defense stood tall. But for us to
come together as a unit and not waver
and get this W, man, it's I think it was
a
it was it was a great one. I think
that's the best thing I can say.
>> You good. How is it preparing for a team
that didn't play a ton of starters and
this week trying to figure out what
they're going to do?
>> I mean like one I think this team like
you didn't I mean we just kind of got to
play what you see and I just kind of
relied on my experience of like you know
just playing playing for Vic once in the
Niners when he was our defense
coordinator just understanding his
philosophy um and just kind of just
involving with the game as it played
out. you know, they they were throwing
different things at us. Uh, and it just
got to the point where, you know, you
just got to play what you see every snap
and, uh, just try to go out there and
execute and I think we did a good job of
that and, uh, pulling together and was
able to finish strong.
>> At this point, you're the most veteran
guy and most tours that you're going to
be in, but is there any point this week
or today when you're talking to some of
the younger guys and you know, how
important regardless of how the rest of
the season is going, the game?
>> Um, I mean, that that's more of a thing
that I'm going to lead by example. Um,
no need to say it. I feel like our
leaders, you know, our [snorts] coaches,
um, the leaders on this team, you know,
they they do a great job of of showing
up every day. And that kind of sets the
presence of what we got to do about our
business. And when guys see me, I just
want them to see a guy, you know, that
just being a light in the room, like a
guy that's grateful to be able to play
this game that that so many me so many
people dream that they can get the
opportunity to do. And I'mma always put
myself back in that kid like mindset of
understanding like how it how it felt
playing in Pop Warner, you know,
dreaming and hoping that one day you'll
play on a Sunday. So to me, I'm just
going to always let that show in my
actions and then and I hopefully, you
know, today we look like we all was on
point. So it worked. And it wasn't just
for me, it's credit to everybody.
>> Josh, what was the call at the goal line
there? You kept it yourself. Was it your
choice or was it
>> Yeah, I had I I had options to keep it
or throw it. Uh, and then, uh, we set it
up well cuz we kept we kept we kept
trying to run in there and they was, you
know, they was they was holding strong
and the looks the looks were just
getting more more and more premier. So,
I thought Cliff did a great job of
timing up when to call it. And then, uh,
when the options was there, you know,
the corner was kind of waiting. I didn't
know if he wanted to come to me or not.
I saw Chris popping in the back of the
end zone. So, if he had ran to me, I was
going to pop it to Chris like I did to
JB and he ended up turning his back. So,
I just kept it.
>> Seemed like you were under center a lot.
Was that part of the design this week?
>> Um, yeah. And then in just the situation
though, uh especially like when we uh
when I dropped the snap and you know
just trying to eliminate, you know,
those those those those mishaps and just
play clean football, give us a chance to
win and we was able to do that today.
>> Seemed like Terry and Debo on the
outside were kind of getting what they
wanted. What did you guys see in those
matchups? And what does it show you with
two veteran guys like that giving you
everything in week 18?
>> Oh man, I'm so grateful for those guys,
man. They showed up all week. uh showed
up all week, showed up on game day and
they was rocking and uh so for them to
really go out there and make the plays
that they did, I feel like it opened it
up. It opened up for a run game in the
second half. Um they start clouding
Terry a little bit more which was good
for us cuz it created some running lanes
for Crod and uh and uh and Bill and then
we was able to, you know, I felt like we
was a little bit more balanced at the
end. Um and then then was able to punch
in some touchdowns and come away
[snorts] with a victory.
>> What did DQ say to you after the game?
Uh he just said, man, he just said he
just said, "Congratulations, man. It was
a brotherhood win, you know, and that
was that's really what he been preaching
all week. Uh love playing for DQ, man.
He's he stick he sticks he sticks to the
purpose and you know, that's a sign of a
great leader and um I know this team,
this organization is going to do great
things because they got the right man
after him."
>> Hey Josh, it's been a lot of movement at
the quarterback position. So, can you
just share like in terms of the
brotherhood, what's the camaraderie that
you all have built in that position
specifically so that you're able to come
in and do your job today?
>> Um, it's it's it's just a it's a great
support system, man. Like, everyone
supports each other. Everyone has each
other's back. Everyone shows love. Like,
and it was there the day I walked in
here. I noticed it. I noticed it with
Sam, with Jay, with Marcus. And then
when Jeff came back, you know, the bond
was there. So, for me, it was just
really just coming in and being myself
and just being an asset to the room in
any way possible. And, uh, you know, the
guys when they were when they were in
there, you know, it was my job to
support them in the best way I could.
And they was always open, which is which
is huge because some I've been around
some places where, you know, guys might
not be as open to you. And, uh, you
know, everybody was open. And then when
I got the opportunity to play, you know,
Marcus supported me in every way
possible. Jay supported me with every
which way possible. Jeff got here, same
Sam, same way. Cliff, BJ, like it's a
great room for quarterback development
here and I think you can see that when
different guys go in there and learn how
to manage the ship.
>> What's been your impression of working
with Cliff this year and what have you
thought of it?
>> Um, awesome. I've never been around
Cliff. Um, never played this style of
offense. Uh, it's a very innovative
offense that get guys open, man. He
knows how to get guys open. Um, he's
very he's always looking to attack the
defense. Um, and I and I've enjoyed just
playing with him and also just how open
he is to our opinions and things that we
are comfortable and not comfortable with
because like my situation, I never
really got to really play for Cliff in
real games like Marcus and Jay has. And
for him to be open to me and responding
to me to the things how I see it and go
out there and call it that way. It was a
big adjustment for him to do that and I
think he responded well and Cliff's a
great coach, man. So, I'm just glad to
be here with him.
Josh, there postgame embrace from
somebody like that from somebody that
meant it more to you than others.
>> Uh I mean my mom, my wife, my two sons
and my brother was here. They were
sitting right behind us and so to have
them come on the field just experience
that like being a dad like a lot of my
kids miss these moments with me bassing
around. And so for them to be able to
just experience embrace the whole
environment of of what comes with this,
you know, I hope I hope I hope I hope it
puts an impression on them, you know,
that like we can do this out of Oakland,
California. We could do this out of
anywhere. But you got to you got to do
your part every day and show up for
yourself and just show up for the people
that you working with. And you know, you
never like God God does the impossible
all the time and just, you know, just
keep your faith and keep going. So
hopefully I learned a lot. I'm looking
forward to having a conversation with
him after this about it
>> was throwing was I saw you juke seven
out and kind of got to the end zone but
that reaction was that just like letting
go of everything?
>> Yeah. Like man, you gotta you gotta
internalize a lot of my position and you
got to stay the course and you got to be
disciplined to a lot of things and you
got to kind of be borderline a little I
guess crazy is the word cuz you got to
but it's now like I'm going use the word
faith like you got to really be faithful
and you got to really listen you like
for me I got to listen to the spirit
when it talks to me because when I came
here in 23 and I had the two concussions
I thought it was over like I thought it
was over and I prayed on it and I just
got closer with God and he just told me
just keep going man just keep going and
don't waver like find take gratitude in
the small victories whether that be
getting a rep whether that be getting a
getting there and just handing the ball
off like those things mean something in
this league and so for me I just focused
on those things and you know was able to
get this opportunity today and I just
want to just go out there and just show
my gratitude and my style of play.
>> Cool. Thanks.
>> All right. Thank you guys. Congrats.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
That was our quarterback Josh Johnson.
Now that's how you end the season. Now
it's time for our toast of the [music]
town presented by what? B Mitch
>> Lash your man D
>> Champagne and Branson Cognac. The
official champagne and cognac of the
Washington Commanders. And this toast of
the town is no other than 17 scary Terry
wide receiver Terry McCorin against the
Eagles. fellas. He is currently number
three all time in career receiving yards
in franchise history, I'm sorry, career
receptions in franchise history verse
the Eagles, passing Bobby Mitchell who
had 70. And he's also number four all
time in career receiving yards in
franchise history verse the Eagles.
Passing Gary Clark who had,4
fellas that boy 17 keeps getting it
done. Tan, I'm tossing this one to you
cuz I got to imagine you on both of
those lists.
>> Yeah, I don't know. I mean know
[laughter] I mean you know London just
told you you know I don't be knowing
half of that stuff but when it comes to
the guys in our division we all have a
team that we excel of you know what I
mean like I had the Cowboys it was one
of those teams had the Cowboys and the
Giants but Terry has been a eagle killer
I mean from day one no matter who they
had their best their second best you
know we we heard some great names in
here that he's went up against and Terry
seems to always show up every time you
play against the Eagles.
>> Terry always shows up. Now, we got to go
to break, but when we come back, we'll
be hearing from Bobby Wagner at the
podium and more from these guys right
here. This has been Command Center
Postgame Live presented by Nissan. We'll
be right back with more after this
break.
[music]
Nissan trucks and SUVs are built for
next level adventure.
Too much gear, dirt,
rock,
sand.
Get in a Nissan truck or SUV and feel
unstoppable. Nissan, [music] number one
in new vehicle quality. Now get 0% APR
for 60 months when financed through
INMAC. Or get up to 5,000 customer cash
on select new models.
I am too young to do my own thing, but I
know they're wrong. You see, mama not
worried and papa never did. I'm just a
little bitty girl like a whole lot of
kids doing my own thing. [music]
>> What would you like the power to do?
>> Bank of America.
>> [music]
>> The best offense
is a great defense.
[music]
Get 100% verified tickets only from
Ticket Master.
[music]
Seats available all season long, even
last minute. [music]
Take it to the house every time. Ticket
Master, official [music] marketplace of
the NFL. The Maryland Lottery Holiday
Raffle is here with your best chance to
win $1 million. Only a limited number of
tickets will be sold. There are also 10
$100,000 [music] prizes.
In fact, there are over 10,000 cash
prizes in all.
The final $1 million drawing is on
January 2nd. So, play the Maryland
Lottery holiday raffle because tickets
are going fast.
At Northwest Stadium, we raise hail
together, cheer together, and trust in
our team together. Northwest is proud to
support the Commanders. And as your
hometown credit union, [music] your
goals are our number one priority. We're
your friends, neighbors, and fellow
fans. And your financial success is our
passion. [music] Become a member today
and let us help you build your next
dynasty. Northwest Federal Credit Union,
where trust matters.
[music]
>> Welcome back into Command Center
Postgame Live presented by Nissan. We
are awaiting head coach Dan Quinn and
linebacker Bobby Wagner. As soon as they
get to the podium, we will take them.
[music] But as we wait, it is time for
our fast play of the game brought to you
by the Maryland Lottery. Please play
responsibly. And you mentioned
Revo earlier. We talked about him in the
pregame as well. He is our fast player
of the game and it's this interception
for 28 yards. B, you said this is his
first interception since what?
>> First since 2020. But the thing about
it, you watch that kid. He has been
unbelievable [music] on special teams
for a long time here. Made the Pro Bowl
with that thing a few years and now
getting a chance to play because [music]
they saw what he was doing. Had some
injuries. He went in and they kept him
in there. Revo [music] will put that tie
on you. He'll make you think twice about
going across the middle. And he picked
that interception off the day and he was
tied for the lead with tackles on the
team. Says a lot about him. says a lot
about Revo and honestly his whole career
says a lot about him fell as we talked
about a little bit in the pregame. He's
a fighter and he's one of those people
that Tana just needs an opportunity. We
saw him kind of stuck on special teams
for a really long time. Injuries forced
him onto that field and hard play forced
him onto that field too. Tann rose to
the occasion.
>> Yeah. I think one of the things about
him that shines bright to me is just
he's he never cared. He he wanted to
play football. He wanted to do what it
took to be a part of this team and made
sure every time he was out here on the
field, he left it on the field. And
that's why he was around for so long.
And then you got to think about it. You
had different coaching staff that
basically had him on that that team. And
and now he's with a new staff and and
they feel the same way that Ron felt
away about him. But I say one thing too,
man. Those the type of guys you need on
your team for you to have a successful
team. You need more guys like that
that's selfless and that's going to go
out there, fly around, make plays,
special teams, defensively, however it
is. whatever you need from me, coach,
I'm there.
>> And that's exactly what Revo does. And
we talked so much about the importance
of special teams and being special. Revo
is a testament to that, man. He earned
his bread and butter on that special
teams and has found a way to make a play
and be I think it's going to be hard to
get him off the field now.
>> It's going to be hard to get him off
there. And the thing about it, listen,
man, you find a way to stay around.
Yeah. You know, uh like I remember coach
Gibbs telling me, the more you can do,
the longer you can play. And Revo has
shown he's very, very valuable as a
special teams player. But this year,
he's shown he's even more valuable now
because he's the type of guy where you
can keep one of him. Yes,
>> you don't have to keep two different
people to play that position. You don't
need to have a special teams guy and
another safety. You got Revo, he can do
both of them. Make sure your agent
understand that when you're going in to
get your contract, but you know, you can
do those things. He is a guy who's
special for a team. And you know, I've
been talking to him for the last three
years. We become kind of close here. I
like to see guys like him because this
guy, when he wasn't sure, he never
stopped working. Mhm.
>> He kept working and the good things
that's happening for him right now is
what you can get when you put the work
in.
>> And this has been great to see him too.
I mean, you look at the Tresway video
where he finds out he's a Pro Bowl.
>> His whole family there. Rebo probably
the happiest one, smiling, cheesing. And
we remember when Rebo found out he was
going to be a Pro Bowler, how much that
meant having leaders like that that have
been through so much. I mean, both of
y'all have been through it being on
Washington for a really long time.
Different regimes, new things going. I
mean, we've only been through three name
changes, right? How important is it to
have guys like that in the locker room
as we move forward with such a young
team trying to turn things around next
season?
>> I mean, guys like that are the staples.
You know, those are the guys those are
the guys you try to go and find and say,
"Let me get let me find more like him.
Let me find more like Terry. Let me find
more like Revo. Let me find more like
some of these guys that that was here
and that's been able to, you know,
withstand some of those ch changes." And
that's what you that's why I say you
give him so much credit because not only
he's he's been here with other coaching
staff, but we just know where he came
from. And it's not easy to be a special
teamer. You know, it's not easy to fly
around there and do some of the things
that he he's done over the past years. I
mean, we we talk highly about him year
after year about how he flies down on
kickoff. They took a little bit of that
out the game for him, but he still shows
up on that. And then he said, "All
right, you take that apart. You kind of
minimize my production on kickoff. Now
I'm going to go out here and do it on
punt team." and then vice versa. So now
to see him finally get his chance to go
out here defensively because someone got
injured. He showed this team, he showed
the whole division that, hey, I got an
opportunity cuz someone got hurt and I'm
going to make sure that's the last time
they take me off the field.
>> When you start talking about culture and
building culture, we all look at a
coach. Yeah.
>> And no, it's players like Ario. It's
players like Terry. It's players like
Bobby Wagner. Those are the guys that a
coach come in and and hitch his wagon to
and say, "Help me build this team. Help
me build culture." Because I guarantee
you when those guys speak, everybody
listens. Because when you are a
performer, when you're a guy that goes
out there and do your job at a high
level, people listen automatically. But
if you're not doing your job, you got to
shush. Nobody want to hear you.
>> And somebody that always does his job
and has been a leader for us these last
two seasons is a guy in Bobby Wagner. It
seems like every time we talk about
Bobby Wagner, he is breaking a record.
He's reaching a new milestone. And as we
said it, he has reached 2,000 tackles.
I'm hearing that he is coming to the
podium. So, we'll talk about him while
we wait to take him at the podium,
fellas. Man, I mean, I I don't think
there's any bigger fans of Bobby than
us, right? Like, we love seeing what he
can do. And it still seems like he got
more to take. B,
>> you know what? I think people
are used to seeing guys. We got him.
>> Oh, we got Bobby right now. Let's go
ahead and take him. Go ahead, B.
[laughter] I was going to let you finish
your thoughts. Look like we got some
time, man. He ain't dead yet.
>> Well, I just say it until he comes up.
People always talk about the older
>> wait for everybody or what?
>> Yep.
>> Let's start with what the win means.
>> Um it's just good to get a win. Um last
time we were here it didn't work out so
well. Obviously circumstances are
different but um you know just feels
good to get a win. um to start the year
off with a win and um just try to end
the season on as positive note as you
can.
>> You entered some pretty impressive
company tonight. Um what does that mean
for you personally to have that kind of
career longevity just to be able to get
that kind of accomplishment? Uh it means
a lot cuz uh you know it was a long time
ago um when I reached out to those guys
um and they were so grateful with their
time um giving me advice, helping me uh
answering any question that I had
spending time with me and so to join a
group with them is just a blessing and
um you know something I'm proud of just
because you know I just tried to apply
um what they taught me as much as I
could and and Um, you know, I was
grateful.
>> Point for you this season. You really
have to fight through some
disappointment to have a day like today
where you guys are still fighting to the
end, you know, maybe it was tougher at
some point.
>> Say one more time.
>> Was there a point in the season maybe
have to fight through frustration to be
able to get to this end of the season to
continue?
>> Um, obviously this season didn't go the
way that we wanted to. Um, but I think
as competitors and, you know, people
that want to win for the city, you had
to just go out there and and uh, put
your best foot forward and that's all we
did. Um, sometimes it worked out,
sometimes it didn't, but um, we can walk
away with with a a lot of positive and
and figure out how to fix things.
>> First, how do you feel that you finished
individually and how does it affect what
you want to do going forward? Uh, I feel
fine and I have not thought about
anything outside of today.
>> Bobby, you've obviously been here two
years. One year was great. One year team
wise wasn't wasn't as great. Does it
give you [snorts]
some confidence that you could if you
did come back or this organiz
organization is close to being able to
flipping it, having a year more like
last year?
>> I haven't thought about any anything
outside today. I'm just uh grateful that
we got a win today and um I like how we
fought and um you know we were able to
kind of close it out from a defensive
standpoint and something to be proud of.
>> What what things did you see around you?
Seen a lot. What things did you see from
this team this year that maybe could
lead to a quicker bounce from?
>> Um honestly I think uh a lot of the the
things that we've we had were a lot of
injuries. Um, we had a lot of, you know,
situations injury-wise that that played
a role and and, um, you know, I think
there's so much talent in this room and
you just have to build on that. I think
there's a lot of young guys um, poised
to make a jump next year and that's
where the injury's at.
>> What's it like to to get to that 2000
number and be able to share it with
obviously around the team?
Now, that that that part is um that part
is special, you know, to be able to to
do that for the city and his jersey and
have him be the guy um that that
presents it to you is is special. Um cuz
I remember when I reached out to him and
I remember um it was no questions asked.
He took my phone call, he answered all
my questions. Um you know, he would
check on me, see how I was doing, and my
whole goal was just try to make him
proud. and I never thought I would be
wearing the same jersey as him. And to
be uh in that same locker room with that
energy and having him be the person to
present that to me is something I'll
never forget.
>> Besides the number two represent
>> um
I don't know. It's a lot of hard work. A
lot of hard work. Uh consistency. Um
it's pushing through injuries um that
people know about that people don't know
about. um is pushing through good times,
bad times. Uh it's is staying committed
to your work, staying committed to your
craft, no matter what people say
outside. Uh you just keep going. And
it's a lot of things that happen behind
the scenes um that people don't know
about, but uh you go out there and you
perform. And you know, I think it just
uh speaks to the people around me. Um my
family, my coaches,
um obviously my teammates, uh cuz none
of this would be possible without all my
teammates over the course of my my
season. I have to have the lineman um
you know, to make sure they keep the
guys off me. Uh you have to have the the
nickel or the wheel or the safety, you
know, turn the ball back to you on
certain fits. Um there's so many things
that that kind of play a part in this
number. So it also represents just you
know the people I've been able to play
with. Um people I've been honored to
play with and um you know this is just
as much as their accomplishments
accomplishment is mine.
>> Tracking tackles in real time can be
tricky. When did you know that you
actually
>> So I didn't I didn't track it you know
um it was my coaches and my teammates
they were telling me. So the first half
they were like, "Man, you're not doing
nothing."
[laughter]
I was like, "Yo, we're in a good spot
though, so it don't matter." Um, but uh,
you know, I think, um, I think George
called down and said he got five and
then, uh, Norton told me and then they
started celebrating and I was just like,
yo, like, let's let's win the game.
Like, let's not have this happen and
lose.
>> When when did you start looking at the
possibility of getting to this number in
your career? Was it before the season?
At what point do you know that, hey, you
got a shot?
>> I don't think you, that's what I'm
saying. I don't think I thought about it
like that. I think uh, you know, I was
told by some of the great linebackers
that a good typical season for a
linebacker is over 100 tackles, you
know, multiple sacks, multiple
interceptions. And so, I would really
just try to go out and do that. And
then, um, you know, first came a
thousand and then, uh, came 1,500 and
then on and on and on. But it was never
something that I um cared about or went
to the season like, "Oh, I got to get
that." It's just I just did my job and
then as I did my job, the people around
me said, "Hey, you itching closer to
this." And you know, I just felt like as
long as I kept doing what I needed to
do, whatever going to happen is going to
happen.
>> You guys didn't
you guys kept repeating. What does that
say about the group, but also about Dan
Quinn and people still playing for
coach? I mean, I just think it's the
culture that we we we built here. Um,
just always competing, always, no matter
what the situation is, good or bad,
because anybody can come out and work
when it's when it's going good. But, um,
through those challenging times, going
out there and still fighting, I think is
big. So, I think it's something that we
can we can uh, you know, build on and
um, you know, proud of everybody in the
building.
>> I know you said you have thought past
today. What are the next couple months
going to look like for you? What sort of
process are you going to go through to
decide kind of your next steps?
>> Uh I have no process, you know, like as
far as like thing like that. I'm just um
grateful and and blessed to be healthy
and um I'm just going to enjoy kind of
seeing the guys tomorrow and things of
that nature and then uh take it from
there. Uh go back to the West Coast and
get some sun.
>> All right. Thanks,
sir.
Final throw.
That was Bobby Wagner. Now, normally we
go to break fellows, but BB cut you off,
man. We got to give Bobby his flowers,
man. So great to see him up there, bro.
Just graduated. Got his masters. Now is
in the history books with two of the
best ever.
>> Look at him, man. He's an accomplished
player. He's probably done everything
you can do at that position,
>> but he's still putting himself through
the rigors to get in shape for this
game. Yeah,
>> this game is not easy for any, but for a
middle linebacker who's normally his
size playing against offensive linemen
that are 6'3, 6'4, 6'5, 300 plus pounds
to get ready for that every year, it
takes a lot.
>> And we talked to London earlier in the
pregame show about what it takes to
always be prepared. Bobby is in what,
year 16, 15, 16?
>> Yeah, some
>> at that position. And I know a lot of
people like make a lot of comments, but
I would just say, think about this. What
have you done for 15 years where you had
to get yourself in shape to deal with
guys that are bigger than you on a
regular basis and you love doing it and
you had the success that he's had? Hey,
let's just give that man his flowers
when he have a chance. Man, he's
outstanding.
>> He sets the tone with his work ethic. He
sets the tone with his attitude and he
sets the tone on and off the field.
Shout out to Bobby Wagner for joining
the race with the London Fletcher and
Ray Lewis. Three future Hall of Famers
right there, fellas. Now, we are still
awaiting head coach Dan Quinn, but we
are going to take a break and when we
come back, we'll be hearing from our
head coach and [music] more from these
guys and even our radio guy, Logan
Paulson. We'll be back with more
commands to the postgame live presented
by Nissan. [music]
[music]
Nissan trucks and SUVs are built for
next level adventure.
Too much gear, dirt,
rock,
sand.
Get in a Nissan truck or SUV and feel
unstoppable. Nissan, [music] number one
in new vehicle quality. Now get 0% APR
for 60 months when financed through
INMAC. Or get up to 5,000 customer cash
on select new models.
>> [music]
>> Trust brings us together as families,
friends, and neighbors. At Northwest
Federal Credit Union, we know your
financial [music] decisions are more
than just signing on a dotted line.
You're putting your trust on the line.
And as life [music] unfolds, we'll be
here for every step of your journey. At
Northwest, [music]
we work to earn your trust every day.
Because this is our community, too.
Become a member today.
Northwest [music] Federal Credit Union,
where trust matters.
[music]
>> [music]
>> almost heaven. [music]
>> Come to West Virginia this season and
put the wonder back into [music] winter.
>> Find miles of uncrowded snowcovered
country to explore [music]
[singing]
>> and cozy cabins and lodges.
All at prices that'll [music] make you
feel warm inside.
>> Find your almost heaven at wvourism.com.
[music]
>> You're watching Command Center Postgame
Live presented by Nissan. Experience the
thrill for yourself today. Shop [music]
nissanusa.com.
Welcome [music] back into Command Center
Postgame Live presented by Nissan. Your
final score 24-7. We are still awaiting
head coach Dan Quinn at the podium. We
will take him immediately, [music] but
until then it is time to do our postgame
delivery brought to you by Pisanos, the
official pizza of the Washington
Commanders. Order now at pisanos
pizza.com. Pizza, wings, and commanders
football. welcoming in the radio guy
Logan Paulson was on the sidelines came
and kicked it with us. Logan, you
started off, man. Who delivered tonight?
>> I'm going to say Josh Johnson. Man, I
really think like obviously he had an
interception, there's the fumbled snap,
but I think overall when you look at his
performance, the big scramble in the low
red, the scramble on third and long,
like those moments, the completions to
Terry, the chemistry that those two had
over the course of the game thought was
absolutely outstanding. And for a guy
who's 39 years old, man, running the way
he did, taking some of those hits, like
hats off to him, man. and the utmost
respect. Like really fantastic
performance. I thought
>> I have to say Crod. Crod's been the guy,
man. We've been talking a lot about our
backfield, you know, the uh the running
back by committee, seeing so many guys.
We start off with Eckler earlier this
year. He went down with an injury. Uh
Crock, we talked about him last year
about just coming in this year being in
shape, having so much opportunity,
[music] and it seemed like every time he
got a little bit opportunity, it was
taken away from him because someone else
shined a little bit. And it was like one
of those musical chairs type of deal.
[music] But he withtood it, man. And and
he was the guy to finish the season off
the right way and go out there and put
up some big numbers plus another
touchdown to give us the victory.
>> Well, I'm going to take it to the other
side of the ball. I'm going to go with
Revo. Uh Revo came out today, he had was
uh tied for lead for the lead with
tackles and also got him an
interception. Uh and like you look at
him, he's had a a tough haul, too, just
like a C-D. A guy who had to go back and
forth for a moment, then found his
footing and he's taken gra a big grasp
of it. I don't think he's going to let
it go.
>> And guys, all those guys deliver now.
While we away here goes Dan Quinn, let's
break it down, right? Let's start with
Josh Johnson cuz I don't know if we
talked about him enough. Logan, one
thing I was pointing out to the guys,
you're talking about his age, right? He
was sacked zero times and a lot of that
has to do with how quickly he was
getting the ball out, but like what be
said, he was using those feet, too.
>> Yeah. I think it's just the experience.
Like that's that's one of those
opportunities where like the older, more
experienced football player knows how to
elevate those guys around him. And it's
not like this, you know, herculean
performance, but it's just very, very
solid. Just getting on base
consistently, understanding when the
ball's got to get out of his hands and
understand how to evade pressure in the
pocket. Like really did some fantastic
stuff, made some big time throws today.
And again, like, you know, we did the
guys that we thought stood up or big
time moments, like his the rapport he
had with Terry.
>> Thinking about how few times he's
probably thrown him over the course of
the season, I mean, it's really just a
testament to Terry and again testament
to Josh and his work ethic.
>> And then look at that offensive line as
well. you know, those guys out there, a
lot of young guys who were filling in
and they played well. They gave him
time. You could see him moving around
and when he had to use his leg, he did.
So, I I like to see that aspect of it
for sure because those young guys may be
the future. You know what I mean? And
you saw them go out there and they play
well against We can say what you want
about the Eagles playing some backups.
They have talent all over that roster.
So, and they play well against them as
well.
>> And Tana Logan brought up an excellent
point which I want to talk to you about
being our receiver here. Josh Johnson
being the third quarterback, he probably
isn't getting a lot of reps throwing to
a guy like Terry McCorin. How tough is
it to find this success that they've
been finding? Cuz I know we see it and
we're like, that's just Terry. That's
just what he does. But can you paint how
really difficult that is for guys to
find that kind of chemistry so quickly?
>> I think we'll probably look at it or
Terry will look at it later on and and
just think about like, wow, that's
that's the third guy I had to sit there
and and him get used to how I'm coming
out of my breaks and how deep I'm going
to be on certain routes. But as a
professional, you don't give it time to
like sit and sit and and and thought cuz
you got to go out there and perform. So
I don't care if it's you coming off the
bench. I got to go out there and and
make sure I'm open. If you're a
quarterback and you understand where
certain routes need to be at, you're
going to throw the ball accordingly.
That mean I need to be there
accordingly. So I've been in plenty of
games, man. We talk about my first year
here in '05 when we had Ramsay as my
quarterback. Manuel, that's my first
year. I was in training camp the whole
entire year with uh Mark Brunell and and
hadn't caught a pass from him. Ramsey go
down and and play 10 of the game. Me and
Mark Brunell went on and had a magical
season that year. So So that that's just
what it is, man. We get played to play
the game, we don't get a chance to think
about what's going on, but I know when
those guys sit down and Terry sit down
and think about all the guys he court
passes from. That's when it set in.
That's when you kind of think about
like, wow, I was had to go out there and
do what I had to do. But it's kind of
hard. You know what I mean? I'm kind of
playing it down because it is what it
is. You can't understand it. I I
understand it, but I still at the same
time I feel like we got to go out there
and get the job done regardless.
>> And I mean, it's really a testament to
Terry and the way the consistency with
which he runs routes like cuz you can
trust him. Like you can trust you can
almost throw it to him in the dark. And
I think that's the thing that makes him
really dynamic is again like you watch
him run a comeback, it's exactly where
it's supposed to be. There's enough
route running nuance to him. There's
enough contested catch ability you can
trust him. And I think like Josh has had
enough experience to know like like kind
of like you and Mark Burell, you always
tell that story like Mark was gonna like
where's Tanner? Let me figure it out.
Like that was what this game felt like.
It's like I know I got a stud out there.
I know where he's going to be. Let's
give him an opportunity to win this
game.
>> You like you being in the batters box
and you're sitting up there and the
pitcher pitches and you're getting ready
for his timing. Josh is the type of guy
he's playing so long [laughter] where
Josh is probably sitting out there
behind everybody when Terry breaks.
Okay, I'm going have this chance one
[laughter] day. I may have this chance
that all of a sudden baming happens.
>> And Tanner, you mentioned Crod as your
guy. Let's talk about Crock right now.
16 carries, 65 yards, and a touchdown.
We have seen him gone through so much in
those first three years of him being
here. I got a feeling now Crod has found
a home in the Burgundy and Gold.
>> I mean, you know what? To be honest with
you, man, and I'm going to put this out
there going forward. I I think coming
into next season, we got to look at him
as running back one. You know, I think
he gets opportunity time and time again
when it comes down to like close,
especially short yardage. And he seems
to be the guy we need to make those
runs. You know, don't get me wrong, I
love Bill and I think he's that he's
that lightning to that thunder that Crod
brings and it'll be a great switch up
with both of those guys back there. But
the opportunities that this guy has had
taken from him and giving back to see
him perform time and time again. Someone
has to say, you know what, I'm going to
reward you for that and let you at least
know coming in, you're the guy because I
because I know that he's going to be
ready for it. You know what I mean? He's
been showing us that he's ready. So,
they need to give him that nod.
>> He's on that last play. He's catching
the ball at the back field as well. What
you see within a C- rod, if the players
block for three yards, he gets four.
Yeah,
>> cuz he's going to get what he gets.
>> Okay, Bill is a different style of
running back. Well, Bill can see that
four and he may miss get two for one
time, but the next time he may go to
distance, but if you need a battering
ram consistently and then you wear
somebody out,
>> Bill could be your closer.
>> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying? Like in
baseball, they got a pitcher that goes
out five to seven innings and then they
bring in a closer. You got two guys
right there that could be special down
the stretch.
>> And fellas, y'all talk about the things
Crod has been through. Let's really talk
about it, man. Before the season starts,
before we trade BR, he's the fifth
running back on the roster. Like, he has
to come and make that. He has to come
and earn his keep. We have seen that so
much. Logan, you are in the film all the
time. When you look at the last three
years of Croat and his progression, what
are you seeing in the film that shows
that maybe he can be an RB1 Tanner talks
about?
>> Well, I think the thing that sticks out
to me about this year specifically is I
feel like he's in really good shape,
right? I think he's running with a
little bit more urgency. there's a
little bit more burst to his game which
again like you can be a powerful runner
but in the NFL man you have to be able
to kind of get in that hole real quick
right as quick as you possibly can and
then the the tough like he's evolved in
terms of being a difficult tackle like
he's got a little bit of kind of lateral
quickness but also when he puts his
shoulders down with that forward lean
like that is a special difficult person
to tackle and bring down and you feel
that be you talked about it three into
four like there was a bunch of times
today where it's like he's hit at the
line of scrimmage and all of a sudden
you're like oh that's second and 10 oh
and you look up and he's like, "Oh,
that's second and seven." Because of his
personal effort. And so, again, like, is
he going to hit the home run? Probably
not. But he does have that just kind of
get on base running style, which is so
valuable to an NFL offense.
>> And think about a day like today, it's
cold.
>> Yeah. No one wants
>> to hit you. Okay. [laughter]
Cro runs the ball and make guys say like
what France made when the tackle was
going. [laughter]
Crod makes people do that.
>> 65 yards and a touchdown for our guy
Crod. Now, you said somebody that
delivered was Jeremy Reeves. I've heard
you guys talk about him. We have not
heard from Logan yet. Jeremy Reeves, a
guy that has just been a staple on
special teams, but then this year we
deal with so many injuries and he
becomes a prime player on our defense.
What have you seen from Hit Logan and
his development and his leadership?
>> Well, I think the thing that sticks out
to me about Jeremy's and I heard Tannon
talking about it is like that special
teams like don't undervalue that. If
you're having a hard time making the
roster, that's a good way to find a
home. Stick around, evolve, learn
defensive principles, and then get your
time to shine. and when it's your time
to shine because you've got this
background of what it means to be a
professional, you can capitalize on it.
So, I think you see and again, he brings
the same physicality on teams to
defense, the tackling, the consistent
tackling that's actually gotten a lot
better from last year to this year,
which is fantastic. And then
>> the interception day is something I
never thought he had in his bag, right?
The ball skills to make that kind of
play. So he's a guy like again that's
one of these special guys that we've
seen throughout our careers throughout
covering the team that when given the
opportunity just gets better and better
and better and learns and continues to
improve and you can't those that
self-starting element to a player you
can't coach it and so like when you have
a guy like that you really got to reward
it and I feel like they've done that
here
>> and it's funny you talk about a guy
getting better what is this year eight
year nine for Jeremy Reeves to see him
continue to get better it's much like
what we see from Bobby Wagner we heard
from Bobby Wagner a little earlier 2,000
that we guys got to talk about. I know
you want to give Bobby some love, too,
on that on that milestone.
>> I mean, I just can't even fathom that.
Like, there's a bunch of milestones like
2,000 yard rusher, 2,000 yard receiver.
Like, the physical violence required for
2,000 tackles, the longevity, the
preparation like Be was talking about,
like you are not right medically in the
head to do that. [laughter] Like, we get
to hang out with Fletch. Like, we get to
hang out with Fletch. Like, like you
were talking about, you're you're
dealing with bigger guys. like you are
getting in 2,000 car crashes in your
life in a 13 years and you and you can
you have the the physical resiliency to
like I cannot think of another metric in
football that shows toughness,
competitiveness and stick to the way
that statistic does. So kudos to Bobby,
man. It's fantastic.
>> Drop the tea.
>> Say stick to stick to sick. [laughter]
>> So sick. Sorry, dropping bars over here.
I wasn't ready for that. And Logan
again, a guy in Bobby. Doesn't look like
he's slowing down. Looks like he could
continue to play. We did not get to hear
his press conference, but love to have
Bobby back, right? Right, Logan?
>> Yeah. And this is the this is the
difficult thing with Bobby because I
think there's a lot of fans, a lot of
people calling for like, hey, young a
youth moving at the position. But I
think if you look at the last five, six
weeks since the Miami game, really like
he's been playing at a really high
level. And so if you are going to bring
him back, does his role change to
accommodate a guy like Jordan McGee
specifically on third down? That's what
I would look to, right? cuz there's no
doubt Bobby can still play, but like
what what is his best utilization? And
to me, it would be on first or second
down. Let's let him let's get him to
like whatever 3,000 tackles, whatever it
takes. But he's he's doing a great job.
>> And it's right. You got the young guys
in there. And Jordan McGee and K Mad.
And speaking of the young guys, Logan,
we got some draft coverage coming up.
It's your time to shine. Let's get into
our road ahead brought to you by Nissan.
At Nissan, we make cars that thrill.
Experience the thrill for yourself
today. Shop Nissan USA.com.
And Logan, usually the road ahead about
the games we got left, but the season's
over. my brother. So, we have some big
dates coming for you because Logan
Paulson will be diving deep into draft
[music] coverage starting next week at
the Shrine Bowl. Logan, tell the fans
what they can expect from y'all this
offseason. I'm looking at these dates
right here. My brother, you are going to
be busy.
>> Very busy. Obviously, Shrine Senior
Bowl, like kind of the big uh, you know,
post college season for like the the
senior football players, potential draft
picks. That'll be a great opportunity to
get to watch football. 87% of those guys
end up getting drafted. And so if you
want to know who's going to be
available, maybe not in the first two
rounds, but down the draft board, that's
a great opportunity to know that. Then
obviously we got the combine coming up
here, which is a great opportunity to
kind of see everybody's height, weight,
speed, the underwear Olympics be. I know
you love that. [laughter] But again, for
us in the draft community, that's a big
day. And so all those things to kind of
help develop our draft board. We're
going to talk about every single
position. Last year we got to 225 guys.
Hopefully this year we get to 300.
That'd be pretty fantastic. So if you
need anything commander draft related,
this is your one-stop shop
>> for sure. And Logan, as you look at
that, cuz we know doesn't just start
now. You've been prepping all year long.
What are you most excited about about
this process? Cuz now the season's over.
Draft time.
>> So, I think the thing for me that's most
exciting is the combination of draft and
free agency cuz this is where you build
a team, right? Like this is how you get
ready for 2026. So, identifying team
needs here in Washington, saying we can
get better here, here, and here. How do
we best do that? Look at the free agency
landscape. How Adam Peters, who did a
great job the last couple years,
addresses that. And then in the draft
with young, talented pieces. And then
can Adam Peters work some magic and find
some more draft picks? All those things
would be really compelling to keep an
eye on.
>> Yes or no question. I'm not asking you
to give me names, whatever. But you know
what the needs are for the commanders?
>> Yeah.
>> Is it lucrative in this draft?
>> So I this is a very interesting draft.
>> Yes or no? Why you got to give me
>> I got to give you this stuff, man. I got
to give you some time. [laughter] We
need a picture. You know what I'm
saying? So in this draft, so you need
receiver. Yes, they're receivers. You
need explosive playmakers. Yes. I do
feel like this year the top 15, top 25,
maybe not as stellar as it's been in
years past, but like with any draft, if
you know where to look and you've got a
front office that can hunt and peck and
find guys that fit your program, dude,
you can find anything in this draft. And
I look at last year's draft
specifically, Connorly, Amos, Lane,
Bill, Crosky, Meritt, and K Madrono.
Four of those guys were huge
contributors this year. If you can hit
that again, you're going to be doing all
right.
>> There we go.
>> And and Beeish, man, put you on the
spot, too. What position of need are you
looking at right now? We've seen so much
football from this team. We have so many
guys that are still banged up. It's feel
like it's kind of hard to evaluate
positions that needed.
>> Yeah, I'm still on the defensive side. I
think pass rusher, you know, I think you
have to deal with that. I still think
you can utilize another uh guy in the
secondary and then you go to the uh the
wide receiver. I just think that you
playmakers at those positions and in
this league, you got to have somebody
that consistently puts pressure on the
quarterback. If you have that on your
team, you can do a lot of different
things with that.
>> And to piggy back off of that and look
at Philadelphia just as kind of a team
that was in the Super Bowl last year and
is in the playoffs this year is the
depth of those positions. There you go.
You need eight defensive linemen. You
need a bunch. You probably five good
wide receivers. And if you have that
again, you can accommodate injury better
and you can make sure you all those guys
are fresh when they're rushing the pass.
>> And Logan, we are waiting head coach Dan
Quinn. You guys talking about the draft
makes me think of something I've seen a
lot of fans talking about and it's
seating. Where we actually end up in the
draft. A lot of people wanted to see a
loss because maybe we would get the
fifth pick or whatever. Logan, when you
look at this where our team sits and you
look at the draft prospects in that top
10, right? Is there a big difference
between being five and maybe seven
eight? Me and Santana were talking about
it a lot.
>> Yeah, I don't really think there's a
huge difference. Obviously, there's
going to be a good player at seven,
there's going to be a good player at
five. I think the one thing is Dante
Moore from Oregon. If he chooses to
declare and there's a two quarterback
draft all of a sudden, you know, with
Mendoza from Indiana, then that top five
becomes a little bit more interesting.
trade potential. But again, like if you
want a good player at five, yep. If
there's a good player at seven,
absolutely. So to me, there's not a huge
difference. And again, you got to think
about each team's individual draft
board. Like our draft board will be
slightly different than Philly's draft
board in terms of prioritizing what
works for us. And so we might end up
getting our second best player at seven.
You know what I mean? I think that's
important for fans to remember that
there's not one sizefits-all in terms of
draft prospect. So 57 doesn't really
matter to me. And fellas, we made it
this whole time without mentioning Jaden
Daniels once, but this was Jaden Daniels
second season. Now he's going into an
offseason. We don't know what his health
status is like, but we know he is
working hard to get back. Logan, when
you look at what you seen from Jaden
from the games he [music] did play, what
do you want him to be focusing on this
offseason as he prepares for year three?
>> Yeah, I think for me it's just about,
you know, can you develop a develop as a
passer in the pocket? I think that's
what I would say. And again, that's not
an indictment on what he's doing, but
just control the football, keep your
eyes downfield, be a playmaker,
>> fellas. Finally at the podium, our head
coach, Dan Quinn. Thank you, Logan.
>> All right. What's up, everybody?
>> Well,
put this down. For 18 weeks, I've been
up here, and I'm certain uh the word
that I've said the most is finish. And
sometimes we did, and other times we
didn't. And it's really important to see
that tonight. Uh to see us finish um
like a super challenging season uh by
the guys. Absolutely. I thought just
fighting their ass off. It's been tough.
Um lost a lot of players to injury and
some really just tough moments and so
for me to see them um there was it was
just cool to see the players who were
able to, you know, to battle for one
another. That's what we said this would
be about. Uh I'm proud of the team
tonight. Um they fought and they
finished and that's what I was looking
for going into it in this like the most
difficult time. U there'll be plenty of
time for reflecting and that's
definitely going to happen soon but I'm
in no way in that space right now. And
so um let's save that conversation for
later this week. Promise I'll give you
all the time I can but I'm not there
tonight. Um but all that said, I'm glad
to open up to questions regarding the
game.
>> What did it mean to see to see that get
that 2000.
>> I was uh like super proud. Um in fact,
it was like a cool moment tonight, John,
that uh I asked London to be in the
locker room as well. So, for only three
players in the history of our game to
have over 2,000 tackles with Ray and
London and Wags now part of it, um it's
fitting. He's the best tackler I've
coached. And so, um,
you know, like to have that happen, like
you could see how important we were for
that. I looked at the stat line at the
half and I was not so, okay, let's let's
split some. Let's get some more tackles.
Um, but in true Wags fashion, um, he
will find a way. Um, he's remarkable in
so many ways. I showed the team
yesterday just got his NBA from Howard
with a 4.0. Like, of course he did.
Like, why would he get a B in anything?
like that's be so unwaglike in so many
ways. So, um I was really happy that
London was there too, John, because um
these are two guys. I said, man, like
don't stand too close. These guys will
tackle you to the parking lot in the
locker room. Like it's what they do. But
um it was pretty rare to have those two
guys together. And so um that was
important for me to have London. I asked
them, "Please come down early so you
could be here um from the radio
broadcast." And uh so to see those two
guys together, different times,
different eras, but um very cool.
>> There's no way you could have obviously
thought when you first saw Bobby that
this would happen, but would you recall
the first thought about what he could
be?
>> Well, that was the best trait that I
saw, you know, going there to see he was
long. And uh we had had some meetings
with some of the players this week that
were thinking of emerging players. I
said, I'd like to show you some of the
early practice and training clips of
what tackling looks like because um
rarely is he out of position, you know,
much like the center fielder that knows
how to track the ball and go after it.
Um very rarely does he overrun a play or
not in the right space. Um and he's
turned out to be a really good blitzer
and that was something that we didn't do
a lot with him early in his career. we I
for the early part, but um because of
his size and his strength that he's
developed, um that's also been a really
strong part of his game. I don't know um
if he had any today, but I thought he
applied good pressure inside.
>> You had other milestones today. Von had
a big sack
and Josh got a win. I just wonder what
those two things meant to you as well.
It did. And uh I spoke to both of them
and uh I could feel let's start with
Josh first just the intensity the work
that he wanted to put in and uh
afterwards you could feel you know his
excitement as head coaches and
quarterbacks the wins and losses they
they get attached to you and so so for
him to have one and fight for it that
was a really big deal. He really put in
the work. You guys probably saw we
played a little bit differently with
Josh compared to um you know Jaden and
Marcus, but it was effective for him and
I think um that was a good sign. And
then for Vaughn um we were just talking
before we had come in about he goes, "I
remember you picking me up. We went out
to lunch together. We talked about some
things and uh man, I'm really like
honored that I got to coach him. I wish
I'd coached him for all the years
because of the uniqueness that he
brings. But, uh, when anybody's really
really good at something, there's a lot
of detail that goes into it. And that's
what I've learned, you know, from him.
And, um, man, I'm I'm the one that's on
the grateful side because I learned a
lot.
>> What What aspect do you think as a pass
rusher maybe do you appreciate him more?
>> I You wouldn't think of his power, you
know, because he's not the biggest guy,
but he's got really good power. He can
get up the field and turn into a guy. So
that would have been something that you
don't often times think of for a, you
know, 250 lb player where he's not, you
know, 270 and can work a guy back. But
because of his legs, John, like he has
got real power down in his lower body.
And so it's a good reminder just because
the guy is not, you know, heavy doesn't
mean he's not powerful through his legs.
And uh he's a great example of that.
This might fall in the reflective
category, but you stood at this turn at
the end of the season in two very
different seasons.
>> Does that give you hope that flipped
around one year, is it doable to flip
around in a single off season again?
Yeah, I'm not there yet like
reflectively, but um I've got high hopes
because of the locker room um to see so
many different pieces in, but um over
the last four weeks, the battle the
fight remained the same. Um by no means
was it clean or turnovers or tackling or
any things that I like. But if you have
your attitude right and they want to
fight for one another, I think that that
alone is a standard that you have to
have to build a championship program.
And no one likes the roller coaster of
year up to year down. But seeing that
kind of fight um for the guys that were
able to do that tonight, that's a big
deal to me.
>> Two or three weeks, we noticed a little
bit of a shift in the offense, whether
it be more hback usage, maybe more
moving the pocket uh with design runs,
under center type stuff. Just various
little items, but really kind of in the
last two or three weeks, just kind of
what has inspired that shift here late
in the season?
>> Yeah, and uh a good bit of it was um
through Josh um and what you know he
would be able to do from the line of
scrimmage. Could we get to some plays?
Could we get to some checks? Um, Coach
Vanio's defense tough, you know. Um,
they play a lot of quarters. They
brought good pressure tonight. Um, as
you get down closer to the red zone,
their red zone defense and red zone
offense, I think, had been one of the
strengths of their club and certainly
one that I study and look at. But, uh,
more than anything, just finding the
best way to feature the players, you
know, and how they can go. There were
some tough runs by Chris. Um, I like the
shots we took to Terry. some of them
resulted in fouls. So, it may not it may
not it won't show up on the stat sheet,
but they were good throws, you know,
outside when you have your chances to
go. And so, um I I'm looking forward to
watching those, but I thought those
were, you know, good shots, you know,
for the time.
>> Hey, coach, could you talk about the
stretch as far as uh you all have the
ball, you go on offense, you score, and
then your defense has to hold them out.
Could you talk about that series right
there?
>> Yeah. Towards the end of the game. Yeah,
I think um that's the finish uh Donna
that I'm referring to to see the defense
finish tonight. Um that was what we
wanted to see to see the offense go down
to get ahead when we you know fell
behind. All right, we go and get your
scores. Um we took some shots on fourth
downs. Um tonight we were able to do
that, but uh more than anything knowing,
okay, this is the time now we got to go
close the game out. And uh for a guy
like Vaughn or Wags in that space um
that's a competitor's time and uh when
he got the first down you know in as we
got through the two-minute um you know
getting some more stops after that I
thought was a really big thing and the
finish that's what um I was proud of at
the end.
>> Got time for one more not to ask like
contemplate yourself. What are the next
couple weeks like for you? We know
you're going to talk with with us and
Adam, but what how do you kind of go
through that? There's a lot um it starts
with the players first and then we go
through what's called like exit
interviews with them and uh you can
learn a lot and I think the first thing
you do um as an offseason begins is you
know where do you improve internally and
the players um that's why we do it we
find out a lot from them what we can do
better how we can do things differently
you go through that with players and
coaches we meet with free agents so
there's a lot of internal work that you
have to do first you know kind of point
the mirror at yourself then you get to
end end. But that's what we'll gain from
tomorrow. We'll meet with the players.
Um and we call those exit interviews.
And so it's not just like, hey, good
luck seeing the offseason.
We try to be
mindful of, you know, what are some
things that went well? What are some
things we need to do differently? And
through the years, I've learned a lot
from players. And uh in fact, most of
the really, really important things have
been from them. And so want to listen
and then take all the information in and
then systematically, you know, put it
together. But it does take time. Um when
you have a season like this where you're
just frustrated and um if I had the hair
like you, I'd pull it out. But um it's
not an option right now. So there's a
lot to go through, but it starts with
the players and tomorrow is an important
day to do that. And uh then we'll start,
you know, the the offseason process,
which goes, you know, pretty lengthy.
All right. Thanks everybody. Appreciate
you guys.
[music]
[snorts]
>> That was our head coach, Dan Quinn. And
fellas, this is a wrap on Command Center
Postgame Line, but also the season that
was. Appreciate y'all so much for tuning
in with us. But just cuz the season over
don't mean the content over. We got a
full slate of shows for you all week
long. And Command Center isn't going
everywhere. Every Thursday on the
Commander YouTube page or catch us on
WSA9 all off seasonason long. I'm your
host Brian Cobbert Jr. here with Brian
Mitchell Santana Mall. Shout out to
Logan Paul for kicking it out with us
with this cold. We are going to get out
of this thing. But make sure you thank
yourselves and pat yourselves on the
back for being the best fans in the NFL,
rocking with us all season long. We'll
see y'all [music] next week on Command
Center.
>> Hey, before the game, Jake said
brotherhood game and start 2026. Man,
that was cool. battling for one another
like a uh there's only one game ball to
go out tonight and I brought one of the
old heads in. So, Fletch.
>> All right, man. Yes, sir.
>> Hey, listen. Um in the history of the
National Football League that's been
played over 100 years, there have been
three players to eclipse the 2,000
tackle mark.
>> Only only three players. So, Ray Lewis,
myself, and today BOBBY WAGNER.
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> THANK YOU GUYS. I appreciate you, man.
Ever since I got out here, man, the love
of the game, you guys helped bring that
back to me. And um you know, I know
we've had um some ups and downs, but I
would never want to go ups and downs
with this group. This group is special.
It means something to me. It's something
I'll always remember. I'm so grateful
for you guys and let's keep pushing.
Tell you about it. [cheering]
[music]
>> [music]